http://www.childsafetystore.com/pages/privacy-policy

Safety Blog
Privacy PolicyWe at ChildSafetyStore.com understand many people are concerned about the safety of transferring their personal information on the Internet. We work hard to ensure your information is safe. At ChildSafetyStore.com, we respect and value our customers and their privacy. The personal information you submit to us is used for purchase processing and account maintenance purposes only. This information is used to better serve our customers and will not be transferred to a third party for any reason.
THIS MIGHT NEED TO BE UPDATED BASED ON SHOPIFY SSL CERTSSecure Shopping GuaranteedYour security is our primary concern. To ensure safe shopping, we use 128 bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption security, which is the highest level of security available today for secure e-commerce transactions. All pages containing your personal information, including credit card numbers, name, and address are encrypted while in transit. That means it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. SSL encryption makes shopping on the Internet the safest way to use your credit card. It is much safer than making a purchase in a store or charging your dinner in a restaurant.
Customer Service
Shipping
Returns
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Submit Feedback
Child Safety Store
1085 SW 15 AVE. E-3Delray Beach, FL 33444Phone: 561-272-8242Fax: 561-272-8289
Sign up for our email newsletter and receive exclusive savings!
Home
Search
About
Contact
Copyright © 2020 Child Safety Store.
Empire Theme by Pixel Union. Powered by Shopify
jcb
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
